(ナルト)多重影分身の術！
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
(角都)影分身を３体…。
Three Shadow Clones...?
(いの)何なの？ あれ…。
What's that?!
(チョウジ)すごい… 高音…
な… なんてチャクラだ…。
What a... high pitched... Chakra!
アイツら 何を…。
What... are they?
《なんだ？ あの術は…。
What is that Jutsu?!
あれをくらったら やばい…。
絶対に ダメだ…》
If I get hit with that... then I'm...
definitely doomed.
風遁 螺旋手裏剣！
Wind Style: Rasen Shuriken!
これで決めるってばよ！
This is the end!
おう！
- Yes!
ボクも加勢する！
(ヤマト)ダメだ。
I'll back him up, too!
No!
(ヤマト)ナルトに近づくな。
巻き添えをくうよ。
Don't get close to Naruto,
or you'll also get caught!
これが 人柱力の九尾の力か。
So this is the power of
the Nine-Tailed Fox's Jinchuriki...
バケモノらしい術だ。
A fitting Jutsu for a monster.
なに!?
What?!
おら!!
(角都)しまっ…。
Damn--!
え…？
What...?
なに？ 勝ったの…？
What? Did he win?
失敗だ…。
Failed...
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
explain to me this happiness
anata ga saikin taiken shita
that you just got to experience?
shiawase wa ittai nan desu ka
or maybe you're so blessed
megumare sugite ite
that you can't even remember it
omoidasenai kamo
that you stand here now
ima koko ni iru koto
that you still live and breathe
iki wo shite iru koto
I realised that they all were miracles
tada soredake no koto ga
just by themselves
kiseki da to kidzuku
you've gotta be extra careful
mijika ni aru mono
with the things nearest to you
tsuneni ki wo tsukete inai to
you know the closer you get to something
amari ni chika sugite
the tougher it is to see it
miushinatte shimai sou
you know the closer you get to something
the tougher it is to see it
and i'll never take it for granted
it's fine to say you'll never give up
oi tsudzukete kita yume
and to keep chasing your dreams
akiramezu ni susumeyo nante
but the more time you spend talking big
kirei goto wo ieru hodo
the less you get done
nanimo dekicha inai kedo
I will press that handful of courage against my heart
hito nigiri no yuuki wo mune ni
and with its help survive another day
ashita wo ikinuku tame ni
and i'll never take it for granted
let's go
Wind Style - Rasen Shuriken!
うっ… うわっ！
(カカシ)さすがは 意外性の忍者だ。
やってくれる… ヤマト！
Always the unpredictable Ninja.
He did it again...
- Yamato!
- Right!
はい！
心臓を いただく。
I'll take your heart.
Damn!
はっ！
クソッ！
Damn it!
はぁ… かっこつけるだけ
つけといて。
Gee... Acting really tough...
ナルトらしいっつったら
ナルトらしいけど。
That is so Naruto...
螺旋手裏剣とかいうから
ピューッて飛ばすのかと思ったら➡
Since it was called Rasen Shuriken
or whatever,
I thought you'd let it fly...
走ってぶつけないとダメなの？
Do you have to actually run and punch?
何だよ！ 当たればすげえんだぞ！
Hey! When it hits the target,
it causes some serious damage!
う～ん。
(ヤマト)螺旋手裏剣といっても➡
It's called the Rasen Shuriken, but...
ゼロ距離で
相手にぶつけないとダメなんです。
you must hit at point-blank range.
だから影分身で陽動をかけるのが
この術の基本だったんですが。
That's why this Jutsu relies on
Shadow Clones as a diversion.
(カカシ)まだ新術の
発動持続時間が短すぎるな。
The duration of this
new Jutsu is too short.
もって数秒か…。
(ヤマト)そんなところです。
It only lasted a couple seconds.
Exactly.
You'll never hit the target with that.
それじゃ 当てられないよ。
あんなヤツ相手に。
Not against someone like him.
That Nine-Tailed kid's Jutsu...
《角都 : 九尾のガキのあの術。
威力は相当ありそうだが➡
It seemed very powerful...
近づかなければ大丈夫だな。
but I'll be safe as long
as I keep my distance.
接近戦を避け 術を持つオリジナルに
常に注意をはらっていれば➡
As long as I avoid close-range combat
and watch the one using that Jutsu,
さほど怖くはない》
I have nothing to fear.
もう一度
オレにやらせてくれってばよ。
Please let me try one more time.
新術で決めてやる！
I'll finish him with my new Jutsu.
You're against that "Akatsuki"!
相手は暁だよ。 また同じことを
やっても かわされるだけよ。
If you do the same thing,
he'll just dodge it again!
一度陽動がバレたらもう ダメだよ。
If he detects our diversion,
we're done for.
みんなで やろう。
Let's fight him together...
確かにな。
この状況 今は５対１だ。
That's true...
Our current situation,
it's five against one.
危ない橋を渡る必要もない。
There's no need to take chances.
《さて どう来る？》
So... what's their next move?
カカシ先生。
Kakashi-sensei...
修業中に
オレに言ったこと覚えてるか？
Do you remember what
you told me when I was training?
うん？
四代目火影を超える
忍は お前しかいないって。
You said you believe
I'm the only Shinobi
そう信じてるって。
who can surpass the Fourth Hokage.
ナルト？
Naruto...
I know teamwork is important.
確かに チームワークは大事だ。
危ない橋ってこともわかってる。
I also know that
this is a very risky path.
でも今オレは その危ない橋を
１人で渡りたいんだってばよ。
Even so, I want to take this risk alone.
向こうへたどり着けなきゃ
オレはいつまでたってもガキのままだ。
If I can't beat this,
I'll never be able to grow up.
So please...
だから…。
だから その橋を
はずすようなことはしないでくれ。
Please...
don't take this path away from me.
フッ…。
ヤマト お前は どうだ？
えぇ。
Yamato, what do you think?
Yeah...
だって まだ見てないですよね。
You haven't even seen it yet,
after all.
以前のナルトとは 別人だってところ。
You haven't seen how
he's a completely different Naruto now.
(カカシ)決まりだな。
Then it's settled...
(サクラ)シカマル…。
Shikamaru...
パックン 今のは!?
(パックン)近いぞ！
Pakkun! What was that?!
They're close!
(飛段)ハハ… ヒャーッハッハ！
なんてザマだ これ…。
This is a sorry state...
オレを こんなにしやがって…！
How dare you do this to me?!
(飛段)ハッハッハッハ…！
テメエには 必ず
ジャシン様のバチが当たる！
Jashin-sama will punish you for this!
ジャシン教により
大いなる裁きが お前に～っ！
A greater judgment will be
handed down by Jashin himself!
(シカマル)そんなもん
怖かねえんだよ。
That doesn't scare me.
オレとお前じゃ
信じてるもんが違う。
We believe in different things.
オレが信じてるのは 火の意志だ。
I believe in the Will of Fire.
(シカマル)だが テメエの神は➡
But your god is not that stupid "Jashin-sama"
or anything.
その くだらねえ
ジャシン様でもなんでもねえ➡
今は… このオレだ。
Now... I will hand down judgment...
オレが 裁きを下す。
テメエ…！
Bastard...!
さっき 言ったよなぁ！
I told you, judgment will be handed down
to you by Jashin-sama!
テメエには ジャシン教により
裁きが下るってよぉ！
なぁ！ ガハハハハ！
その裁きを下すのは オレだ！
And I will carry out that judgment!
I only need teeth to take care of you!
テメエなんて 歯だけで十分だ!!
よく噛んで バラバラにしてやるぜ！
I'll chew you up into little pieces!
(パックン)見つけたぞ！
We found you!
(シカマル)増援か…
けど ひと足遅かったな。
Reinforcements, huh?
But you were just a bit too late...
な… なに？ シカマル！
Wh-What?!
アンタ １人で暁やっちゃったの!?
Shikamaru...
You defeated an Akatsuki by yourself?
(サイ)この人 案外すごいんですね。
You're more impressive than I thought.
(シカマル)まぁな…。
I guess...
今回ばかりは 何がなんでも
ってヤツだったんでな。
I just had to do this myself,
no matter what.
そうよね…。
That's right...
向こうは どうなってる？
What's happening with the others?
(サクラ)私たちは
すぐ こっちへ向かったから…。
We came straight here, so...
(サイ)急いで 合流しよう。
Let's rejoin them quickly.
うわ… うぅ！
あ！ シカマル！
Shikamaru!
ねぇ 大丈夫？ 今 治療を…。
Hey, are you okay?
I'll heal you right now.
…このくらい 問題ねえ。
でも…。
This is no big deal...
うぅ…。
But...!
もう 仲間が傷つくような
面倒くせぇことは➡
I don't like troublesome things
that hurt my friends.
ごめんだからな。
…あ。
(シカマル)急ごう。
うん。
Let's hurry.
Yeah.
《みんな 無事でいて…》
Guys, please be okay...
いけ ナルト。
オッス！
Go, Naruto.
Right!
《また あのガキでくるか。
That kid's going to attack again...?
念のため 遠距離タイプに
かえたほうがいいな》
Just to be safe, I should switch
to a long-range attack style.
あっ…。
うわ…。
体型をかえただけじゃなく
チャクラも かなり練りこんでる…。
He didn't just change
the shape of his body.
He's built up quite a bit of Chakra.
ナルトの術に対応するためだな。
It's to counter Naruto's Jutsu.
影分身の術。
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
《きたな…》
Here he comes...
できた！
It's ready!
飛んだ！
He flew!
《後ろの陽動の影分身は 無視だ》
I can ignore the diversionary
Shadow Clones behind me.
《狙うは オリジナルただ一人。
I just need to aim for the original.
あの術さえ つぶせば怖くない》
I've nothing to fear if
I can just smash that Jutsu...
ダメだ！ 読まれてる。
No! He's reading him!
《やはり 遠距離攻撃か！》
I knew he'd go with a long-range attack!
ナルト！
Naruto!
よし…。
All right!
《なに!? 影分身だと？》
What?! That was a Shadow Clone?!
Huh?!
《角都 : コイツ…。
陽動の中にオリジナルを…》
He mixed himself in with
the diversionary Clones!
あたり～！
Eat this!
ぐっ…。
(ヤマト)爆風が来るぞ！
The blast is coming!
うわぁ～!!
《攻撃回数がケタはずれだ！
That was an extraordinary amount
of attacks.
写輪眼でも見きれなかった》
I couldn't even count them all
with the Sharingan.
《カカシ : なんて術だ…》
What a Jutsu...
す…。
すごい…。
- Awe...
- Awesome.
Naruto...
You...
You... finally...
All right... I did it.
what made me think
kondo wa itsu aeru ka nante
how can you say that with a straight face
sonna kao shite yoku ieru tte
when you asked we will meet again
omotteta yo nande darou
any time you talk to much I don't get it
any time shaberisugi no k y
for a moment I see your bluff and I cry
chirari miseru tsuyogari na i cry
do my tears even work on you?
namida no kouka wa dore kurai
I keep saying "I want to be loved"
watashi nari ni aisaretai
in my own special way but you still don't get the hint
afureru no ni kimi ga mienai
this nagging feeling I feel
nidoto kimi ni aenai
that I'll never see you again...
sonna ki ga suru nda
I wish I could tell you but I can't find the words
tsutaetai no ni umai kotoba miataranai
maybe I'd rather listen to you lie
watashi tabun uso demo ii no ni
I can't even say "don't leave me"
ikanaide mo ienai yo
when you let go of my hand
nigitteta te ga hanaretara
will you forget someday?
kimi wa itsuka wasurechau no
about me
watashi no koto
I wish I could tell you but I can't find the words
tsutaetai no ni umai kotoba miataranai watashi tabun
maybe I'd rather listen to you lie 'cause I can't even say "don't leave me"
uso demo ii no ni ikanaide mo ienai yo
Next Episode
Shizune, did you notice that?
《カカシ : ナルト… お前…。
You mean Naruto-kun, right?
Yes.
I wonder what it is.
お前 ついに！》
I've seen various cases up until now.
ハァ ハァ… ヘヘッ！
But I've never seen anything like that.
What's happening with
the body Kakashi brought back?
よし！ やったぜ！
I have already sent it for an autopsy.
Tell the person in charge
to give it top priority!
Next episode: "The Price of Power"
The Price of Power
みんな 元気かな！
今日 挑戦するのは これ！
How're you guys doing?
This is what we're going to try today.
くちよせの術？
A summoning Jutsu.
"LET'S ALL TRY IT! SUMMONING JUTSU"
そう！ 時空間忍術の一種で➡
Summoning Jutsu?
Yes! It's a space-time Jutsu
契約をかわした生きものを
好きなときに呼び出す術だよ。
where you make a contract with an animal
and summon them whenever you want.
みんなは まだ 口寄せ動物と
契約をしていないから➡
You guys haven't made
a contract with an animal yet,
今回は 印の練習をするよ。
so we'll just practice the seals today!
(カカシ)必要な印は…。
These are the seals you'll need...
Boar! Dog! Rooster! Monkey! Sheep!
あとは 呼び出したい場所に
チャクラを練って 手を突き出す！
Then you build up Chakra and
slam your hand down
焦らず 正確にやるのがポイントだよ。
on the spot where you want
to summon your animal.
It's important to do it correctly
and not rush.
それじゃ やってみよう！
はい！
Now, let's all give it a try!
亥 戌 酉 申 未！
Okay. Boar! Dog! Rooster!
Monkey! Sheep!
手を突き出して！ どんっ！
Slam your hand down.
よぅ！
呼ばれて飛び出た パックンじゃ！
Hi! I'm Pakkun.
I rushed here since I was summoned!
- Ooh!
- Awesome!
術の成功に必要なのは
たゆまぬ努力と 修業！
To succeed, all you need is patience,
effort and training!
あのナルトだって➡
はじめから ガマ親分を
呼び出せたわけじゃないからね。
It's not like Naruto could summon
the Chief Toad right from the start.
たくさん修業して
この術をものにしろ！
Train hard and master the Jutsu!
それじゃ バイバ～イ！
Okay, bye-bye!